When you look, it piles up tightly, tightly, forming a great ring.
The people around them must face the deadly cold wind.
The people inside can keep warm with body heat.
However, the people within the circle must constantly change.
Slowly position the people on the outer perimeter to the center of the circle.
If someone remains on the perimeter for a long time
I'll freeze to death
The people inside will be exposed to the cold wind.
Now
For penguins, the fat and downy feathers around their mouths help retain warmth.
However, the human body has no mechanism to protect against such cold.
Therefore, everyone must constantly stretch out one leg and squeeze their calf.
In this way, miserably exhausting oneself.
According to a news report, everyone will freeze to death within a few hours.